ICICI General is quite liked.
Two-three things are happening for the company sale.
First thing, we have seen the loss ratios which are
very important
for the insurance company in general. This ABET means they make every
effort to reduce it
in the second half and it will be significantly reduced. So in the
second half, F23 and the first half, F5, F24,
you will see a significant reduction in loss issues,
which will
prove the climb significantly. Secondly, I think
Vijendra should
look at a portfolio of products, it
seems constructive. The benefits of retail health have gone
beyond the bank's shelter.
Definitely, retail health is going forward.
And in motor insurance,
premium growth is
expected to be quite good. And the last
ratios I was talking about, both for
group 10, well ahead, motor.
Thirdly, the interested scenario will
actually help investment returns.
ICICI General Care, which
follows the growth and probability of insurance, will see a
significant increase in it.
And the packing crop business, they
want to keep it up to 5%, which Vaidya said a few
years ago, and this link which is
combined fibres, is above 105%, solving
series 2.47 times, and what we are expecting is that we will get
70%
in the second half, we think,
but it can be
remembered,
and the first one was Shrikant Chauhan's call on Canara
Bank, in fact, this call of Canara Bank, I
think, must have been discussed at least 30 or 84 times since morning,
see the strong structure in the entire banking space,
leading this move, Mana Jaiswal ji's
position was, I am long and almost
in the range of 2020, and
Metropolis Prakash is doing
and ICICI Lombard, here is
Mayuresh ji's call, who is long, picking
in the well market Nifty is
18245, that is, if you compare the technical level to
level, then it has exactly done a
bisex at this time.  It has its own
importance, this is its behavior, you can
roughly understand that for the
first time after 15th of December, this flat
slightly with positive
last u average Nifty is
expressing the expectation of being express, here you have the
bisex on your screen
and remember Bank Nifty also
its 43 47, today in the market, there was that
blend of all the sectors in which I was
running, in which banks were running, in which
if you see NBFC was running, in which if
you see today, Doctor Lal Path Lab Metro
Police is also running, friend, that time was
going on, when there was some change, but you
see, today the market pattern, everything is running,
today the technical of Nifty is only yours, at this
time you should have about 20 demo,
so see, I was waiting for exactly this thing and
I had already mentioned that as long as
Nifty keeps trading above 18000, the
undertone will remain, only you have to
wait for the breakout, I believe that
now from here you have to go to 18400 and above.  You will get to
see stars up to 18480, so
in my opinion because I normally talk about last
expiry, last week's
expiry, then Nariti's
18300 comes and you will take D Manipal option, it is trading at 242,
you should buy there,
buy with a stoppage of 190 and
upset the target big, now you can see targets up to 350 375
in the 18300 call option of 25th January,
so you
should definitely buy on Nifty current,
you have a long, now ask for 280 exponential on Nifty,
let's do one less thing, we
talked about many tricks, we talked about four, there was a
delegated discussion on it, now let's
talk to the entire Barot Bro market,
2030 in this special conversation, in the conversation, come
Outlook to zero to three, today we have
a special guest with us
for the discussion of cmdpl group, always yes hello, welcome
to the program, first of all
I would like to welcome you Varsha  Best
wishes for 2023 for your personal life, for your
professional career, for
your clients, for everyone, you will
see, may the West be auspicious, how am I approaching
this year in which so far the
bass